<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wiki on</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/</link><description>Recent content in Wiki on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/introduction/</guid><description>Docs # Use the left hand menu to navigate through the Boom.Army docs.
Boom.Army app # The app is live at app.boom.army.
Boom.Army brochure site # The brochure site can be accessed at boom.army.</description></item><item><title>Season Challenges</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/season-challenges/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 12:04:48 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/season-challenges/</guid><description>Taxonomy # Here is the taxonomy and meaning of the language for the first Boom Heroes Season Challenge.
Season Challenge - A duration of 4 weeks over which each of the NFT Action Card Challenges need to be completed.
Season Challenge Pass - The #BoomHeroes generative NFT that will give you access to the Season Challenge competition. There will be 4777 Boom Heroes available for minting at a cost of 0.</description></item><item><title>The 1303 OG NFT</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/1303/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 11:59:31 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/1303/</guid><description>There are 1303 NFTs in total in existance, and they will receive a 1303 split share of 20% of our Market Place fees in perpetuity. They were minted on app.boom.army during the month of February 2022.
1303 NFT Benefits # 1303 split share of 20% of our Market Place fees in perpetuity First on platform Community DAO channel Bragging rights of being the first members on the first Solana Social platform White List tokens # All White List i3o3&amp;hellip;3bos tokens minted at 1.</description></item><item><title>Roadmap</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 12:05:41 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/roadmap/</guid><description>Our Vision # To be the place for Solana NFT owners to gather and connect around all things NFT To add commerce to Social Content and allow Creators to get paid for the value they produce To remove the middle-man so 100% of Content value goes to the Creators and Hosts engaged in delivering it To enable anyone, regardless of race, creed, or colour to speak freely To build a platform that augments the human communication experience rather than hacks it for commercial gain To decentralize and democratize Social Media on blockchain and make it anti-fragile Upcoming features # The ability to mint, display and sell NFTs in your gallery Deliver communities, roles and experiences based on the NFTs you hold in your wallet Decentralise and open source our API to enable developers to build Social Media variant apps on top of Boom.</description></item><item><title>Whitepaper</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/whitepaper/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 12:05:02 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/whitepaper/</guid><description>NOTE: This document is under development. Please check regularly for updates!
Introduction # Social Media has been a primary driver of the Web2 era. Large centralized organizations have grown up on the back of social media platforms, typically offering a free experience for users to share their data with each other. The shared data provided by users is then stored on central servers and monetized by the same organizations, and through this model many of those companies have grown to become some of the largest most profitable companies in the world.</description></item><item><title>Alpha launch</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/alpha/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 12:04:38 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/alpha/</guid><description>Alpha is live!!! # TLDR; - Head over to app.boom.army and you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to login using the wallet specified when you registered.
NB
You&amp;rsquo;ll need &amp;ldquo;test-net $SOL&amp;rdquo; to pay the tiny network transaction fees. You can get as much as you need for free here. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have $BMA tokens you will be able to post still, but you won&amp;rsquo;t be able to interact or get reactions on your posts.</description></item><item><title>Ignition</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/ignition/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 12:05:15 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/docs/prologue/ignition/</guid><description>Inspiration # Web2 spawned the Social Media craze. Large centralized organizations have grown out of these social media platforms, where users share their data for free. That data is monetized by these companies, and they&amp;rsquo;ve made a boatload of money in the process. The problem for users is that they don&amp;rsquo;t typically see any profit from their valuable data. This is the environment boom.army has an opportunity to disrupt.
Solana allows boom.</description></item></channel></rss>