<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.boom.army/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>💥Build Diary 24💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-24/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 13:12:51 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-24/</guid><description>The Relaunched Boom GitHub Commit History Unveiled # Over the past few weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been hard at work to improve some of the core features and tooling of Boom. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share a behind-the-scenes look into the commit history of my both the back and front end GitHub repositories, which offer insight into the various enhancements and fixes I&amp;rsquo;ve implemented.
One of my primary focuses has been streamlining the deployment and building processes.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 23💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-23/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 13:12:51 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-23/</guid><description>What I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to since Jan # Since January, I&amp;rsquo;ve been keeping myself busy with various projects and collaborations, contributing to the blockchain and technology space in different ways. Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick rundown of what I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on:
CAW Studios: I had the opportunity to work with CAW Studios for two months, during which I collaborated on several projects and had the pleasure of working with a first class team with huge ambition.</description></item><item><title>A Secure Approach to Storing Private Keys and Transacting in Solana</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/a-secure-approach-to-storing-private-keys-and-transacting-in-solana/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 14:12:51 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/a-secure-approach-to-storing-private-keys-and-transacting-in-solana/</guid><description>And let me tell you, the crypto game is not for the faint of heart. In this blog post, we will explore a few different ways to ensure that your Solana transactions and storage are as secure as possible, because in this wild west of digital assets, you can&amp;rsquo;t be too careful.
Why Security is important # Let&amp;rsquo;s get one thing straight, cryptocurrency is vulnerable to hacking and other forms of cybercrime.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 22💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-22/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 06:40:56 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-22/</guid><description>Time just absolutely flies in this space. Every time I&amp;rsquo;m back on the keys bashing out a blog post I can barely believe how much has happened in the last couple of weeks and how quickly it&amp;rsquo;s gone.
FUD in full force # Anyone who&amp;rsquo;s been on CT and Boom will have seen discussion around the absolute shit storm of FUD that is currently being hurled around. The FTX collapse kicked it off, and every few days since then there seems to be a new issue for people to wring their hands over.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 21💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-21/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 06:40:56 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-21/</guid><description>Are you still alive anon? Are you still here? I&amp;rsquo;m still here and I&amp;rsquo;m still building Boom. Nothing has changed for the long term thesis on Solana as far as I&amp;rsquo;m concerned. It&amp;rsquo;s the fastest production Blockchain Layer 1 at scale, with the best community and developers in crypto period. Boom is committed to continuing delivery indefinitely and will always do so as long as Solana remains the best product in the biz.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 20💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-20/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 06:40:56 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-20/</guid><description>How to unpack a failed launch? Currently launching an auction house on Solana is very much still a case of chewing a bunch of glass. It&amp;rsquo;s time to do a bit of an autopsy on the last weeks #BoomOnes Auction House launch and tell the story for future learnings and to preserve it for posterity. We&amp;rsquo;re living through history folks.
How did we get here? # Back in February, Boom launched an NFT called The 1303 OG.</description></item><item><title>💥Ad praesens tempus💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/ad-praesens-tempus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 07:40:56 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/ad-praesens-tempus/</guid><description>Never a dull week in Solana. With the advent of Aptos, all the ruggers, shillers and grifters jumped ship basically overnight and suddenly there was a beautiful calm across the ecosystem. Many cried out in FUD - the ones who relied on these sorts to pump their bags. But the OGs always realized that those bags had no utility, and the day of reckoning always comes for the ones who lie, cheat and steal.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 19💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 14:40:56 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-19/</guid><description>It feels like years since I last wrote a dev diary, but it&amp;rsquo;s only been 10 weeks. The big news and reason for the quiet spot is our CEO Quiet-Salad/Dingo has stepped aside so I&amp;rsquo;ve been somewhat distracted while we completed the formalities associated with that.
I&amp;rsquo;d personally like to take the opportunity to thank Quiet-Salad for his involvement, hard work and dedication over the last year. We remain firm friends and although this is the close of one chapter, the book is long and who knows what the future holds.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 18💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-18/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 14:40:56 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-18/</guid><description>Boom Heroes on Moonrank # You can now search through the traits and rarities of Boom Heroes on MoonRank. It&amp;rsquo;s a fantastic tool.
It&amp;rsquo;s time to Pivot # Let&amp;rsquo;s be clear - Boom is an ongoing experiment to figure out how Social Media works on chain with Solana. Rather than closing our doors and testing with a select group, we&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to open the gates and do everything in prod. This has meant that the feedback and success (or failure) of everything has been immediately apparent.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 17💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-17/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 15:10:10 +1200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-17/</guid><description>As the bear market ticks on we continue to build and upgrade features on the platform.
Boom Heroes Market Place Live # This week we launched our Boom Heroes NFT collection Market Place on Magic Eden. The final collection count of Boom Heroes in the wild is 777. We haven&amp;rsquo;t decided what to do with the remaining 4000, but for now it&amp;rsquo;s as if they never existed as they&amp;rsquo;re locked up and unaccessible in the Candy Machine and they&amp;rsquo;ll stay there indefintely.</description></item></channel></rss>