<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://boom.army/docs/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>💥 Build diary - 13 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-13/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 04:40:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-13/</guid><description>This release sees enough updates to warrant a new minor version of the platform, and we&amp;rsquo;re now at v0.6.0. Here&amp;rsquo;s the things Boom has delivered since the last update.
News feeds are LIVE! # How hard is it to keep up with what&amp;rsquo;s going in the Solana space? Really bloody hard given that a week seems like a year. But not to worry, we&amp;rsquo;ve got your back fam. We&amp;rsquo;ve been scouring the web for the best Solana content and news and now you can see it right in the global feed without having to even leave Boom Army.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - 12 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-12/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 11:36:06 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-12/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s the things Boom has delivered since the last update.
Updated the entire Candy Machine v2 platform # The Candy Machine from Metaplex received some heavy upgrades (many with breaking changes) so I dug into the codebase and upgraded the whole thing. It was a sizable job but now the Candy Machine has bot and spam protection. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping one day we&amp;rsquo;re going to need this, but until that day happens I&amp;rsquo;m going to keep on quietly building and delivering value to the platform for our faithful community.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - 11 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-11/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 15:36:06 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-11/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on the MP build with another dev and in the downtime between code reviews I&amp;rsquo;ve also been able to deliver some serious upgrades to the platform.
Upgrades # The upgrades delivered include:
React v17 to v18 Added Glow Wallet integration Added Slope Wallet integration Material UI Library (MUI) from v4 to v5 Upgraded the Snackbar messaging across the site to MUI Added reply status to the NFT Messaging Channels Glow Wallet # We&amp;rsquo;re currently in the process of helping out a fellow Solana Community member who is doing a screencast of how Glow Wallet works.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - 10 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-10/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 15:36:06 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-10/</guid><description>It was a bit of a mad rush to hit the April 15 deadline for the Boom Hero NFT mint, and over a single 14 hour day all the work was completed to build the traits into 4677 images (more on that number later), loaded the Candy Machine, verified all the image files, rebuilt the launch page on app.boom.army, and launched the project.
Since then my day job ramped up and we had a crazy busy period where an upgrade of the large platform I&amp;rsquo;m responsible for caused a whole raft of NPM package compatibility issues.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - 9 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 15:36:06 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-9/</guid><description>Boom now has all the building blocks in place that will under-pin our Social Media platform. A lot of the effort that has gone in to date has been building out the &amp;ldquo;Social&amp;rdquo; features and now Boom has two types of social engagement constructs:
Twitter style news feed Telegram style chat channels (secured by NFTs) Now the real challenge is one of content and delivering on the &amp;ldquo;Media&amp;rdquo; part of the equation.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - week 7/8 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-7/8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 15:41:35 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-7/8/</guid><description>Today is day 8 for me, and while the overall experience has been pretty much just low energy and mild flu symptoms, I&amp;rsquo;ve spent most of the week in bed asleep, eating chicken soup, and dosing up on Vitamins. Hence the late entry for the dev diary and no real updates in terms of dev delivery.
In spite of that we have a few things to report, especially as we gear up towards the launch of the Boom Heroes Season Challenges that are getting very close.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - week 6 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 15:41:35 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-6/</guid><description>Those features that are built and read to go are:
NFT Community DAO Channels The NFT minting tool - you can now mint NFTs to create your own DAO Communities The third feature that we&amp;rsquo;re currently finishing is:
Comment threads for NFT Community DAO Channels During the last few weeks while I&amp;rsquo;ve been building these out, I&amp;rsquo;ve realised a few things. Namely that we&amp;rsquo;re going to end up with two different types of content threads.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - week 5 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 11:50:39 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-5/</guid><description>The majority of the work to date has gone into the NFT Communities, and I can now announce that it is FUNCTIONALLY COMPLETE!!! That means that for every NFT collection you have in your wallet, you&amp;rsquo;re going to be able to select it as a private channel and Meep to other NFT hodlrs in your own exclusive NFT group. We&amp;rsquo;re also making improvements to the &amp;ldquo;Mint your own NFT&amp;rdquo; functionality so that you can create your own collection of NFTs, and then users can join YOUR OWN NFT CHANNEL.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - week 4 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 15:29:20 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-4/</guid><description>I think this tweet sums up my thoughts on it best.
By far and away the biggest news since the last update is we&amp;rsquo;ve officially welcomed @Flamulus to the team as our Marketing/Community Manager go to guy. Although he needs no introduction as he&amp;rsquo;s been doing the hard :mahi: for a long time around these parts with his phenomenal artistic skills. I have to say, it&amp;rsquo;s an absolute pleasure to be able to have someone like him in this roll.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - week 3 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 15:30:42 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-3/</guid><description>So without further ado here&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s been completed in week 3:
Migrated the entire app theme enabling fine grained control over theme customization Migrated all CSS elements to app theme elements Updated and smoothed the mobile UX on the back of theme upgrades Added notifications for all emojis and content without the need to use @ Completed The Seasons framework doc for Season 1 of our first Boom Heroes NFT Completed inked elements for 37 of the Boom Heroes Generative NFT release Reworked The Distributor Action Card Boom Hero Completed Badgemon Action Card Boom Hero Completed inking Discus Max Action Card Boom Hero Upgraded and optimized Notification database queries Upgraded the postgresQL stack performance Actively interviewing for a Community Manager Paid out over $2000 USD in $BMA tokens It&amp;rsquo;s been a huge week, and for all our kiwi browser users, you&amp;rsquo;ll notice the improvements to the mobile UX experience.</description></item></channel></rss>