<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://boom.army/docs/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>💥Build Diary 20💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-20/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 06:40:56 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-20/</guid><description>How to unpack a failed launch? Currently launching an auction house on Solana is very much still a case of chewing a bunch of glass. It&amp;rsquo;s time to do a bit of an autopsy on the last weeks #BoomOnes Auction House launch and tell the story for future learnings and to preserve it for posterity. We&amp;rsquo;re living through history folks.
How did we get here? # Back in February, Boom launched an NFT called The 1303 OG.</description></item><item><title>💥Ad praesens tempus💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/ad-praesens-tempus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 07:40:56 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/ad-praesens-tempus/</guid><description>Never a dull week in Solana. With the advent of Aptos, all the ruggers, shillers and grifters jumped ship basically overnight and suddenly there was a beautiful calm across the ecosystem. Many cried out in FUD - the ones who relied on these sorts to pump their bags. But the OGs always realized that those bags had no utility, and the day of reckoning always comes for the ones who lie, cheat and steal.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 19💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 14:40:56 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-19/</guid><description>It feels like years since I last wrote a dev diary, but it&amp;rsquo;s only been 10 weeks. The big news and reason for the quiet spot is our CEO Quiet-Salad/Dingo has stepped aside so I&amp;rsquo;ve been somewhat distracted while we completed the formalities associated with that.
I&amp;rsquo;d personally like to take the opportunity to thank Quiet-Salad for his involvement, hard work and dedication over the last year. We remain firm friends and although this is the close of one chapter, the book is long and who knows what the future holds.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 18💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-18/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 14:40:56 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-18/</guid><description>Boom Heroes on Moonrank # You can now search through the traits and rarities of Boom Heroes on MoonRank. It&amp;rsquo;s a fantastic tool.
It&amp;rsquo;s time to Pivot # Let&amp;rsquo;s be clear - Boom is an ongoing experiment to figure out how Social Media works on chain with Solana. Rather than closing our doors and testing with a select group, we&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to open the gates and do everything in prod. This has meant that the feedback and success (or failure) of everything has been immediately apparent.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 17💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-17/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 15:10:10 +1200</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-17/</guid><description>As the bear market ticks on we continue to build and upgrade features on the platform.
Boom Heroes Market Place Live # This week we launched our Boom Heroes NFT collection Market Place on Magic Eden. The final collection count of Boom Heroes in the wild is 777. We haven&amp;rsquo;t decided what to do with the remaining 4000, but for now it&amp;rsquo;s as if they never existed as they&amp;rsquo;re locked up and unaccessible in the Candy Machine and they&amp;rsquo;ll stay there indefintely.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 16💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-16/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 15:57:00 +1200</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-16/</guid><description>Two big new features were delivered this week, and the build delivery is picking up as we head into the end of the second quarter of the year.
Search functionality # You can now search Meeps, Tags and Users on platform as a complete overhaul of the search functionality was delivered. It&amp;rsquo;s fast and functional and was necessary to setup the architecture for our news feed which is essentially a filter on Meeps.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 15💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-15/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 16:06:18 +1200</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-15/</guid><description>In the last 2 weeks Harkl has been working hard to deliver a bunch of Boom NFT upgrades.
NFT PFPs are live # We&amp;rsquo;ve shipped NFT Profile Pictures. It&amp;rsquo;s a simple 3 step process to use any NFT in your gallery as a PFP:
Go to your Profile page Click on any NFT in your gallery Select &amp;ldquo;Set as Profile Picture&amp;rdquo; Check out a 1 minute screencast showing how it works in Kiwi Browser</description></item><item><title>💥 Build Diary 14 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-14/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 10:42:00 +1200</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-14/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s no secret that the last 9 weeks have been brutal across the board in Crypto with everything down bad.
The state of NFTs and Solana # Add to this the number of low quality and knock-off NFT projects that have crowded into the space in the same timeframe, and it makes for a boiling pot of pretty nasty proportions. It&amp;rsquo;s the sort of environment where you get to see the true colors of a community and the report card isn&amp;rsquo;t looking good.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - 13 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-13/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 04:40:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-13/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve just ticked over 22k posts on Boom Army which is a pretty big milestone IMO.
This release sees enough updates to warrant a new minor version of the platform, and we&amp;rsquo;re now at v0.6.0. Here&amp;rsquo;s the things Boom has delivered since the last update.
News feeds are LIVE! # How hard is it to keep up with what&amp;rsquo;s going in the Solana space? Really bloody hard given that a week seems like a year.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - 12 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-12/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 11:36:06 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-12/</guid><description>While the market has been on fire, I&amp;rsquo;ve been quietly getting on with building.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the things Boom has delivered since the last update.
Updated the entire Candy Machine v2 platform # The Candy Machine from Metaplex received some heavy upgrades (many with breaking changes) so I dug into the codebase and upgraded the whole thing. It was a sizable job but now the Candy Machine has bot and spam protection.</description></item></channel></rss>