<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>harkl on</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/contributors/harkl/</link><description>Recent content in harkl on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 08:12:51 +1300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.boom.army/contributors/harkl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>💥Build Diary 35💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-35/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 08:12:51 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-35/</guid><description>Hello friends,
I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share with you the latest updates we&amp;rsquo;ve been working on. It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy period, but we&amp;rsquo;ve made some significant strides.
Enhancing User Experience # We&amp;rsquo;ve made several tweaks to improve your experience. We&amp;rsquo;ve fixed the issue with the &amp;lsquo;Read More&amp;rsquo; button being wrongly positioned on Safari, and made it look more consistent across the platform. We&amp;rsquo;ve also added a subtle text shadowing and restyled the shiny pill for a sleeker look.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 34💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-34/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 08:12:51 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-34/</guid><description>Full steam ahead!
Enhancements and Bug Fixes # We&amp;rsquo;ve made several enhancements to our platform. We&amp;rsquo;ve upgraded our dependencies, made some style changes to the home header, and fixed a bug with the document title not working properly. We&amp;rsquo;ve also experimented with a new UI, made some quick fixes for small screens, and improved the positioning of the text expander.
New Features # We&amp;rsquo;ve introduced some new features that I believe you&amp;rsquo;ll find useful.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 33💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-33/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 08:12:51 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-33/</guid><description>Hello friends,
I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share with you the latest updates Boom has rolled out. As usual I&amp;rsquo;ve been working way too many hours across multiple proijects, but I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled with the progress we&amp;rsquo;ve made.
Enhancements and Fixes # We&amp;rsquo;ve made some significant improvements to the search command. It now disappears as expected, making your user experience smoother. We&amp;rsquo;ve also fixed a bug with hashtags opening account sheets, and another one related to submenus.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 32💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-32/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 08:12:51 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-32/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share with you all the updates we&amp;rsquo;ve made in the latest release of our software. I&amp;rsquo;ve been working tirelessly to bring you a smoother, more polished experience, and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to walk you through the new features and improvements.
Design Improvements # We&amp;rsquo;ve made some significant improvements to the look and feel of our app. One of the first things you&amp;rsquo;ll notice is the enhanced copy for interactions on replies.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 31💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-31/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:12:51 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-31/</guid><description>Hello, you beautiful freaks,
You ever wake up in the heart of the desert, the weight of last night’s choices resting on your shoulders, only to decide you&amp;rsquo;re going to tame the wild software beasts? Well, that&amp;rsquo;s been my trip these past few weeks. Grab a whiskey, light that cigarette, and let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the chaos that unfolded.
The Savage Reality of Digital Landscapes # In the heat of the neon-lit night, several glitches reared their ugly heads:</description></item><item><title>I'm done with twitter</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/im-done-with-twitter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 08:12:51 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/im-done-with-twitter/</guid><description>Over the last few months I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed that my reach and voice has got smaller and smaller. It seems like a common story for many too, as I can no longer connect with and keep track of all the Solana peeps that I used to know and love. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure we realise how big a point of failure Twitter is for the Solana community as a whole. But it&amp;rsquo;s increasingly hard to keep up with new developments in the Solana space on the Xird App.</description></item><item><title>The road to decentralisation</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/the-road-to-decentralisation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 08:12:51 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/the-road-to-decentralisation/</guid><description>Into decentralisation # As you all know one of the long term goals of Boom is to have a decentralized social experience. By far my biggest bugbear with the app currently is that it runs a centralized postgres instance on AWS. Not ideal and not decentralised at all!
With the advent of Threads choosing the open source federated social protocol ActivityPub and the positive reaction from the Solana community around this I feel like decentralised social infra has a clear winner, and now is the time to embrace that specific technology.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 30💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-30/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 08:12:51 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-30/</guid><description>So there I was, waiting to commune with the universe. I was about to unleash a series of updates to shake up the Solana DAO space, which will hit the streets like a thunderclap. Get ready to get a whole lot of Juju all in one place, because we&amp;rsquo;re in for one wild ride.
Riding the DAO Messaging Wave # Slap your own face and say Rammalammadingdong, because DAO messaging is about to be released.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 29💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-29/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 08:12:51 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-29/</guid><description>Greetings, Oddballs and Outcasts,
Brace yourselves for a manic expedition through the pulsating veins of our latest tech concoctions. For those wild-eyed enthusiasts tracking our pursuit of reigning supreme in Solana&amp;rsquo;s DAO terrain, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a gonzo-esque exploration into a week that&amp;rsquo;s been as chaotic as a pack of bats in a strobe-lit cave.
Reimagining Interactions: Tripping Down the Digital Rabbit Hole # We&amp;rsquo;ve been hammering away at our Meeps feature like a crazed sculptor on a caffeine bender, tweaking and fine-tuning until it&amp;rsquo;s as sharp as the hallucinatory visions from last night.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 28💥</title><link>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-28/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 08:12:51 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://docs.boom.army/blog/build-diary-28/</guid><description>Alright, My Fellow Midnight Coders,
Hope this digital letter finds you all in the best of spirits. Yours truly has been battling the fiercest strain of flu this past week, a condition fit to give an electric shock to a dead horse. So the delivery was a tad slow, like a beat-up jalopy limping up a San Francisco hill, but fear not. We&amp;rsquo;ve still churned out a slew of updates that I&amp;rsquo;m just dying to spill.</description></item></channel></rss>