<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>harkl on</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/contributors/harkl/</link><description>Recent content in harkl on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 15:10:10 +1200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://boom.army/docs/contributors/harkl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>💥Build Diary 17💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-17/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 15:10:10 +1200</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-17/</guid><description>As the bear market ticks on we continue to build and upgrade features on the platform.
Boom Heroes Market Place Live # This week we launched our Boom Heroes NFT collection Market Place on Magic Eden. The final collection count of Boom Heroes in the wild is 777. We haven&amp;rsquo;t decided what to do with the remaining 4000, but for now it&amp;rsquo;s as if they never existed as they&amp;rsquo;re locked up and unaccessible in the Candy Machine and they&amp;rsquo;ll stay there indefintely.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 16💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-16/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 15:57:00 +1200</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-16/</guid><description>Two big new features were delivered this week, and the build delivery is picking up as we head into the end of the second quarter of the year.
Search functionality # You can now search Meeps, Tags and Users on platform as a complete overhaul of the search functionality was delivered. It&amp;rsquo;s fast and functional and was necessary to setup the architecture for our news feed which is essentially a filter on Meeps.</description></item><item><title>💥Build Diary 15💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-15/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 16:06:18 +1200</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-15/</guid><description>In the last 2 weeks Harkl has been working hard to deliver a bunch of Boom NFT upgrades.
NFT PFPs are live # We&amp;rsquo;ve shipped NFT Profile Pictures. It&amp;rsquo;s a simple 3 step process to use any NFT in your gallery as a PFP:
Go to your Profile page Click on any NFT in your gallery Select &amp;ldquo;Set as Profile Picture&amp;rdquo; Check out a 1 minute screencast showing how it works in Kiwi Browser</description></item><item><title>💥 Build Diary 14 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-14/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 10:42:00 +1200</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-14/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s no secret that the last 9 weeks have been brutal across the board in Crypto with everything down bad.
The state of NFTs and Solana # Add to this the number of low quality and knock-off NFT projects that have crowded into the space in the same timeframe, and it makes for a boiling pot of pretty nasty proportions. It&amp;rsquo;s the sort of environment where you get to see the true colors of a community and the report card isn&amp;rsquo;t looking good.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - 13 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-13/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 04:40:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-13/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve just ticked over 22k posts on Boom Army which is a pretty big milestone IMO.
This release sees enough updates to warrant a new minor version of the platform, and we&amp;rsquo;re now at v0.6.0. Here&amp;rsquo;s the things Boom has delivered since the last update.
News feeds are LIVE! # How hard is it to keep up with what&amp;rsquo;s going in the Solana space? Really bloody hard given that a week seems like a year.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - 12 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-12/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 11:36:06 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-12/</guid><description>While the market has been on fire, I&amp;rsquo;ve been quietly getting on with building.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the things Boom has delivered since the last update.
Updated the entire Candy Machine v2 platform # The Candy Machine from Metaplex received some heavy upgrades (many with breaking changes) so I dug into the codebase and upgraded the whole thing. It was a sizable job but now the Candy Machine has bot and spam protection.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - 11 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-11/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 15:36:06 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-11/</guid><description>The Market Place build is about 80% complete and in spite of a few road blocks we&amp;rsquo;re making good progress and you can expect delivery soon.
I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on the MP build with another dev and in the downtime between code reviews I&amp;rsquo;ve also been able to deliver some serious upgrades to the platform.
Upgrades # The upgrades delivered include:
React v17 to v18 Added Glow Wallet integration Added Slope Wallet integration Material UI Library (MUI) from v4 to v5 Upgraded the Snackbar messaging across the site to MUI Added reply status to the NFT Messaging Channels Glow Wallet # We&amp;rsquo;re currently in the process of helping out a fellow Solana Community member who is doing a screencast of how Glow Wallet works.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - 10 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-10/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 15:36:06 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-10/</guid><description>Two weeks ago we launched Boom Heroes.
It was a bit of a mad rush to hit the April 15 deadline for the Boom Hero NFT mint, and over a single 14 hour day all the work was completed to build the traits into 4677 images (more on that number later), loaded the Candy Machine, verified all the image files, rebuilt the launch page on app.boom.army, and launched the project.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - 9 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 15:36:06 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-9/</guid><description>Boom now has all the building blocks in place that will under-pin our Social Media platform. A lot of the effort that has gone in to date has been building out the &amp;ldquo;Social&amp;rdquo; features and now Boom has two types of social engagement constructs:
Twitter style news feed Telegram style chat channels (secured by NFTs) Now the real challenge is one of content and delivering on the &amp;ldquo;Media&amp;rdquo; part of the equation.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - week 7/8 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-7/8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 15:41:35 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-7/8/</guid><description>Today is day 8 for me, and while the overall experience has been pretty much just low energy and mild flu symptoms, I&amp;rsquo;ve spent most of the week in bed asleep, eating chicken soup, and dosing up on Vitamins. Hence the late entry for the dev diary and no real updates in terms of dev delivery.
In spite of that we have a few things to report, especially as we gear up towards the launch of the Boom Heroes Season Challenges that are getting very close.</description></item></channel></rss>