<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Harkl on</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/contributors/harkl/</link><description>Recent content in Harkl on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 11:50:39 +1300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://boom.army/docs/contributors/harkl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>💥 Build diary - week 5 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 11:50:39 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-5/</guid><description>The majority of the work to date has gone into the NFT Communities, and I can now announce that it is FUNCTIONALLY COMPLETE!!! That means that for every NFT collection you have in your wallet, you&amp;rsquo;re going to be able to select it as a private channel and Meep to other NFT hodlrs in your own exclusive NFT group. We&amp;rsquo;re also making improvements to the &amp;ldquo;Mint your own NFT&amp;rdquo; functionality so that you can create your own collection of NFTs, and then users can join YOUR OWN NFT CHANNEL.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - week 4 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 15:29:20 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-4/</guid><description>I think this tweet sums up my thoughts on it best.
By far and away the biggest news since the last update is we&amp;rsquo;ve officially welcomed @Flamulus to the team as our Marketing/Community Manager go to guy. Although he needs no introduction as he&amp;rsquo;s been doing the hard :mahi: for a long time around these parts with his phenomenal artistic skills. I have to say, it&amp;rsquo;s an absolute pleasure to be able to have someone like him in this roll.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - week 3 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 15:30:42 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-3/</guid><description>So without further ado here&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s been completed in week 3:
Migrated the entire app theme enabling fine grained control over theme customization Migrated all CSS elements to app theme elements Updated and smoothed the mobile UX on the back of theme upgrades Added notifications for all emojis and content without the need to use @ Completed The Seasons framework doc for Season 1 of our first Boom Heroes NFT Completed inked elements for 37 of the Boom Heroes Generative NFT release Reworked The Distributor Action Card Boom Hero Completed Badgemon Action Card Boom Hero Completed inking Discus Max Action Card Boom Hero Upgraded and optimized Notification database queries Upgraded the postgresQL stack performance Actively interviewing for a Community Manager Paid out over $2000 USD in $BMA tokens It&amp;rsquo;s been a huge week, and for all our kiwi browser users, you&amp;rsquo;ll notice the improvements to the mobile UX experience.</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - week 2 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 15:31:47 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-2/</guid><description>Going to keep this short and snappy @everyone so you can get max info for minimum time spent:
Boom.Army is in the process of being funded! A very well known VC wants to bulk buy $BMA and some 1303 OG NFTs OTC (direct from us) Dingo is talking to other VCs and on the back of our first funding we&amp;rsquo;re in a strong position to negotiate Harkl has written the first draft of the &amp;ldquo;Seasons&amp;rdquo; brief (see attached).</description></item><item><title>💥 Build diary - week 1 💥</title><link>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 15:36:06 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://boom.army/docs/blog/build-diary-week-1/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of the core things happening at the moment to keep you in the loop:
On the back of sales of The 1303 OG, we&amp;rsquo;ve hired more developers to deliver NFT Channels and the Market Place The design is complete for the Market Place and the NFT Channels (see attached images) We&amp;rsquo;re in talks currently with a VC that is interested in buying all remaining 1303 OGs direct from us (OTC) We&amp;rsquo;re working on our first generative NFT which is going to serve as the first Season Pass (loads more detail to come on this) There&amp;rsquo;s going to be 3 separate Season 1 task based NFTs and we&amp;rsquo;re drafting details around this We&amp;rsquo;re looking to hire a marketing/design/social manager to run comms as we do delivery (see attached PDF and let us know if you know of anyone who fits this brief)</description></item></channel></rss>